padsquad.com 2019-08-16

# PRIVACY POLICY – Padsquad

PadSquad LLC is committed to respecting the privacy rights of its customers and other users of the PadSquad LLC Website (all capitalized terms not defined in this Notice have the same meanings as in PadSquad LLC’s Website Terms of Use). PadSquad LLC created this Privacy Policy to give you confidence as you visit and use the Website, and to demonstrate its commitment to fair information practices and to the protection of your privacy. This Privacy Policy is only applicable to the Website, and not to any Third-Party Websites, which, as further explained below, may have data collection, storage and use practices and policies that differ materially from this Privacy Policy. By using the website, you represent and warrant that you have read and understood, and agree to the terms of, this privacy policy. If you do not understand or do not agree to be bound by this privacy policy, you must immediately leave the website.

#### ELIGIBILITY TO USE WEBSITE

The Website is hosted and operated from within the United States. As stated in the Terms of Use, use of the Website is restricted to United States residents 13 years of age or older. PadSquad LLC does not intend to, and will not knowingly, collect information from or about individuals located outside the United States or individuals younger than 13 years of age. If we are made aware that we have received such information from someone under 13, we will use reasonable efforts to remove that information from our records.

#### INFORMATION COLLECTION PRACTICES

Through our Website, we collect, anonymous, Non-Personally Identifiable Information (“Non-PII”). Non-PII is information that cannot by itself be used to identify a particular person or entity, and may include your IP host address, pages viewed, browser type, Internet browsing and usage habits, Internet Service Provider, domain name, the time/date of your visit to this Website, the referring URL and your computer's operating system. We collect this Non-PII data in order to deliver more relevant advertising to internet users and to help PadSquad LLC and PadSquad LLC’s licensors and suppliers better understand who is using the Website and how they are using it. By identifying patterns and trends in usage, PadSquad LLC is able to better design the Website to improve Your experience, and to serve You more relevant and interesting content and advertisements.

#### HOW IS THIS INFORMATION COLLECTED?

To collect this anonymous, Non-PII, PadSquad LLC uses Cookies and Pixel Tags, both of which are widely used on the Internet.

#### COOKIES

Cookies are small text files that contain a string of alphanumeric characters. When you visit a website or view an ad, cookies are sent through your web browser and stored on your computer.

#### PIXEL TAGS

Pixel tags are small images or strings of code on a web page. Pixel tags allow the operator of the web page, or a third party who serves the pixel tag, to set, read, and modify cookies. We use cookies in conjunction with pixel tags in our Platform for ad delivery and reporting purposes and to help make the online advertisements you see more relevant to you.

OPTING OUT FROM COOKIES If you prefer that PadSquad LLC does not collect non-personally identifiable data about your website visits for the purpose of delivering targeted advertising, please see below. When you opt out, we will place an opt-out cookie on your computer. The opt-out cookie tells PadSquad LLC not to use your information for delivering relevant online advertisements. Please note that if you delete, block, or otherwise restrict cookies, or if you use a different computer or Internet browser, you will need to renew your opt-out choice. If you refuse cookies, you assume all responsibility for any resulting loss of functionality.

#### PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION

This Privacy Policy applies only to Personal Information gathered by means of the Website. We may collect Personally Identifiable Information (“PII”) from this Website when you choose to provide it to us. PII is any information that can be used to identify or locate a particular person or entity. This includes, but is not limited to: name, address, telephone number, mobile number, or email address. For example, you may choose to send us PII about yourself in an email or by completing an online form on this Website. We use this information only to contact you to respond to your inquiry. Once collected, we will store your PII for a reasonable time for record keeping purposes. The information is deleted as space requires or in the normal course of business.

Other Disclosure: PadSquad LLC discloses Personal Information under the following circumstances: By Law or to Protect Rights - PadSquad LLC discloses Personal Information when required to do so by law, or in response to a subpoena or court order, or when PadSquad LLC believes in its sole discretion that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of PadSquad LLC, third parties or the public at large. Business Transfers Bankruptcy - PadSquad LLC reserves the right to transfer all Personal Information in its possession to a successor organization in the event of a merger, acquisition, or bankruptcy or other sale of all or a portion of PadSquad LLC assets. Other than to the extent ordered by a bankruptcy or other court, the use and disclosure of all transferred Personal Information will be subject to this Privacy Policy, or to a new privacy policy if You are given notice of that new privacy policy and an opportunity to affirmatively opt-out of it. Personal Information submitted or collected after a transfer, however, may be subject to a new privacy policy adopted by PadSquad LLC successor organization.

#### DELETING YOUR PII

If you'd like us to delete any PII that you have provided to us on this Website, please send your request to us at privacy@padsquad.com and we will process your request within a reasonable period of time after receipt.

#### SECURITY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

PadSquad LLC has implemented and maintains reasonable security procedures and practices to protect against the unauthorized access, use, modification, destruction or disclosure of Your Personal Information.

#### THIRD-PARTY WEBSITES

PadSquad LLC neither owns nor controls Third-Party Websites. Accordingly, the operators of Third-Party Websites, including without limitation Vendors, are under no obligation to comply with this Privacy Policy. Before visiting or providing information to a Third-Party Website, You should inform Yourself of the privacy policies and practices (if any) of that Third-Party Website, and should take those steps necessary to, in Your discretion, protect Your privacy. PadSquad LLC is not responsible for the actions of these third parties, including their privacy practices and any content posted on their web sites. We encourage you to review their privacy policies to learn more about what, why and how they collect and use personal information. PadSquad LLC adheres to industry recognized standards to secure any personal information in our possession, and to secure it from unauthorized access and tampering. However, as is true with all online actions, it is possible that third parties may unlawfully intercept transmissions of personal information, or other users of the Site may misuse or abuse your personal information that they may collect from the Site. PadSquad LLC uses third-party advertising companies to serve our ads on the Site. These third-party advertising companies employ cookie and Pixel Tags to measure and improve the effectiveness of ads for their clients. To do so, these companies may use anonymous information about your visits to our website and other websites, but will not collect any information which can personally identify you or can be linked to you. This information can include: date/time of banner ad shown, the banner ad that was shown, their cookie, and the IP address. This information can also be used for online preference marketing purposes. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads and collect information when users visit our site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements on our site, other websites and other forms of media about goods and services of interest to you. If you want to prevent a third-party advertiser from collecting data, currently you may either visit each ad network’s web site individually and opt out or visit the NAI gateway opt-out site to opt-out of all network advertising cookies. [Click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/what-are-my-options) for the NAI gateway opt-out site.

  * For details on how to opt out of interest based ads, or location-based ads on iAd, visit Apple's support site: <https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT202074>
  * For details on how to opt out of interest based ads on Google, visit Google's support site: <https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922?hl=en>
  * For details on how to opt out of interest based advertising from Microsoft, visit Microsoft's support site: <https://choice.microsoft.com/en-US/opt-out>

#### ADHERENCE TO INDUSTRY BEST PRACTICES

We strongly value the privacy of our users and comply with the regulations set forth in the NAI's Code of Conduct. If you have any questions about these practices please contact us at privacy@padsquad.com
